Kheel, Theodore W. Speeches and Articles 6021/005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Roberts, Benjamin C. Should CB be Revamped? Monthly Labor Review, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A. Forward The 1971 Transportation Bond Issue (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Rocky Man Kheel collaborates with NY Times and Union MisleadershipNew Solidarity News (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Ross, Irwin. The New York Newspaper Strike. The Progressive, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Rushton, William Faulkner, Cable Networking in new York State, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  Oct 29
- Rushton, William Faulkner. The Case for American Two Satellite Networking (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Rushton William Faulkner. Project Metro Lick, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Russel, Kathleen, ed. Welcome Wagon Community 40th Anniversary (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Russel, Kathleen, ed. Welcome Wagon community Winter-Spring, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Rutter, William A. Labor Law 2nd ed, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Salute to Bob Considine Program, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  March 29
- Savas, ES and Sigmund G. Ginsburg. The Civil Service: A Meritless System? (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Scale of Prices, Newspaper Branch, NY Typographical Union No. 6 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Schuyler, Philip N. National Union-Publisher Parleys Urged By Flynn, EandP, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  April 13
- Schuyler, Philip W. New York Strike Mediator Urges Bargaining Reform EandP, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Schuyler, Philip Kheel Quits Job as NY Press Mediator, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Scupi, Richard. Early Experience with Group Legal Services (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Seidman, Joel Alfred G. Edge, and Lane Kelley. Attitudes of Hawaiian Hugher Ecl (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Semlow, Walter J. How to Grow Management Talent. The Iron Age, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- seventeenth Annual Executive Management Institute on Personnel and Industrial Relations Program (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Shapiro, Fred C. Profiles. The New Yorker Magazine, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Shinn, Roger L, ed. The Search for Identity: Essays on American Character (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Shostak, Arthur B. Race Relations: Questions and Answers for Personnel Men (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Shreveport Bar Association Construction and General Laborers Local Union No. 229 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Shreveport Bar Association Laborers Local Union No. 229 Prepaid Legal Services Plan A Compilation (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Shreveport Bar Association Plan for Prepaid Legal Services Intermediate Report of Southwest Admin. (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Shreveport Bar Association Plan for Pre-paid Legal Services: Intermediate Report of Southwest Administrators, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Sixteenth Annual National Strategy Seminar Program of US Army War College (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Soho Television. The Artists Television Network: Soho Television Presents Press Kit (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Solomon, Eric Either/ OR? Both/And?: CB ad Academic Senates (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Somers, Gerald G., ed Industrial Relations Research Assn. Series Proc. Of 25th Aniv Meeting (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Somers, Gerald G, ed. Industrial relations Research Assn. Series Proc. Of 26th Annual Winter Meeting (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Somers, Gerald G. ed Proc of 19th annual Winter Meeting Industrial Relations Research Assn. (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Somers, Gerald G., ed. The Development and Use of Manpower Proc. Of 20th Annual Winter Meeting (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Southwest Legal Foundation Institutes Author's Manual (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Spokes: In the Wheel of the Rotary Club of NY, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  April 30
- Stack, Dave. Legal Services: An Evolving Union Benefit. AFL-CIO Federationist, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Stanford Law Review, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Stanley H. Ruttenberg and Associates, Inc. Multiple Choice/Careers for the Future (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Stanley, David T. The Impact of Unionism on Public Administration (Box 9, Folder 30)
- State Charter Revision Commission for New York City Final Report (Box 9, Folder 31)
- State of Maine, Senate. An Act Extending Collective Bargaining Rights to University of Maine Employees (Box 9, Folder 32)
- State of New York. The Transportation Bond Issue Means Progress (Box 9, Folder 33)
- State of New York. City of New York. Mayor's Advisory Transit committee. Report September 9, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- State of New York City of New York. Special transit Committee. The Co-ordination of Public Transportation (Box 9, Folder 35)
- State of New York City of New York Special Transit committee. The Effectation of the Reduced Work Week (Box 9, Folder 36)
- State of New York. City of New York. Special transit committee. Transition to a 40-hour Week (Box 9, Folder 37)
- State of New York. City of New York. Transit Fact-finding Board. Report to Hon. William O'Dwyer, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  may 31
- State of New York. City of New York. Transit Fact-Finding committee. Report to Hon. Robert F. Wagner, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  May 17
- State of New York. Department of Environmental Conservation. Environmental Plan for New York State (Box 9, Folder 40)
- State of New York. Department of Transportation. Facts About Transportation Bond Issue Proposition One. (Box 9, Folder 41)
- State of New York. Department of Transportation. Planning Division. Prehearing Draft of the Statewide Master Plan (Box 9, Folder 42)
- State of New York. Department of transportation. Statewide Master Plan for Transportation in New York. Vol. 1 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- State of New York. Metropolitan Transportation Authority. 1968-1973 the Ten-year Program at the Halfway Mark (Box 9, Folder 44)
- State of New York. New York City Transit Authority. Some Facts and Figures (Box 9, Folder 45)
- State of New York. Senate. An Act to Amend the insurance Law, In Relation to Legal care Insurance (Box 9, Folder 46)
- State of the Art = New Technology in 1973. Convention of the Associated Press Managing Editors Association (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Statutory Plan Recommended by the New York Port Authority to Improve Waterfront Labor Conditions (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Stein, Abraham. The fiction that P.A.T.H. is a Deficit - Ridden or "Loss" Operation (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Stein, Abraham. The Port of New York Authority: Financial Accounting and Reporting Processes Examined and considered - A Draft Report (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Stern, Robert A/ and Nancy Stern. An Introduction to Computers and Information Processing (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Stewart, Margaret. Removing Obstacles to Automation (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Stieber, Jack. Employee Organization in State and Local Government (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Stuyvesant and INA Offer Group Legal Plans (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Summary of Preliminary Recommendations of the State charter Revision commission for New York City (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Summary Report of the New York Building and Construction Industry's EEO Affirmative Action Programs (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Talks by Doesburg, Kheel to Place Existing MPS, PLS Annuals in April. The Impact, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  March 16
- Taylor, George W. Should Collective Bargaining be Revamped? Income Policy and the Price System. (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Teamsters Local 20 Legal Defense Fund (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Ted Kheel: Why I Won't Run. Manhattan Tribune, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  March 22
- Theodore Kheel On: How to Cool Conflicts. Yours, Your Family's, Your Company's Tomorrow (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Theodore W Kheel et al v. The port of NY Authority. Memorandum of Law Submitted in Opposition to Defendant's Motion to Dismiss (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Theodore W. Kheel v. The Port of New York Authority. Plaintiff's Memorandum in Support of Motion for Summary Judgment (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Time, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  June 15
- Times Talk, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- title VII. Of the Civil Rights Act: Effect of Equal Employment Opportunity Law on Management and Labor in NY State (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Today's Man of Leisure. Esquire, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Townsend, Ed. Interview with Theodore W. Kheel. Christian Science Monitor, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Townsend, Ed. Introduction. Is There a Practical Alternative to Collective Bargaining? (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Training Agreement Between NY Building and construction Industry Board of Urban Affairs Fund and the State of NY and City NY (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Trial: The National Legal Newsmagazine., 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  March/April
- Ulman, Lloyd. Should Collective Bargaining be Revamped? Inflation Policies and Collective Bargaining (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Unconsolidated Laws, Port of New York Authority (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Union's New Legal Service Brings Justice to Many of our Members (Box 10, Folder 26)
- United National. Centre for Human Rights. Human rights Fact Sheet No. 10: The Rights of the Child (Box 10, Folder 27)
- United Nations. Centre for Human Rights. Fact Sheet No. 12: The Committee on the Elimination of Racial Discrimination (Box 10, Folder 28)
- United Nations. Centre for Human Rights. Fact Sheet No. 4: Methods of Combating Torture (Box 10, Folder 29)
- United States Congress. An Act to Amend the Labor Management Relations Act of 1947., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- United States. Department of Labor. Federal Plan to Boost Minority Construction Employment Imposed on Chicago. Navs., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- United States Department of Labor. Labor Department Extends Philadelphia Plan. News, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  Dec 28
- United States. Department of Labor Is the Strike Outmoded? (Box 10, Folder 33)
- United States Department of Labor. Some Facts Related to a City in Flux - An Appraisal (Box 10, Folder 34)
- United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics. Proc. Of North American Conf. on Labor Statistics, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  June 16-20
- United States. Department of Transportation. National Transportation Planning Manual, 1970-1990 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- United States. Department of the Treasury. Internal revenue Service. 1975 Federal Tax Forms (Box 10, Folder 37)
- United States. Department of the Treasury. IRS. Application for Recognition of Exemption Under Section 501 (3) (Box 10, Folder 38)
- United States Executive Office of the President. Office of Management and Budget. Standard Industrial Classification Manual, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- United States. National Commission on Technology, Automation and Economic Progress. Adjusting to Change. Appendix III. Technology and the American Economy (Box 10, Folder 40)
- United States. National commission on Technology, Automation and Economic Progress. Technology and the American Economy (Box 10, Folder 41)
- United States. National commission on Technology, Automation and Economic Progress. The Outlook for Technological Change and Employment Appendix Vol. 1: Technology and the American Economy (Box 10, Folder 42)
- The University is St. John's 1982-1983 President's Report (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Collective Bargaining Today: Proceedings from the Collective Bargaining Forum - 1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Collective Bargaining Today: Proceedings from the Collective Bargaining Forum - 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining Today: Proceedings from the Collective Bargaining Forum - 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions - Theodore Kheel (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions - Theodore Kheel (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Transit and Arbitration A Decade of Decisions - Theodore Kheel (Box 11, Folder 6)
- US Industries, Inc. In the USI News., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Aug - Sept
- United States Trust Co. of New York v. The State of New Jersey. Civil Action Stipulation (Box 11, Folder 8)
- United States of America v. Universal CIT Credit Corporation. Brief for appellees (Box 11, Folder 9)
- US vs. General Motors Corp. Trade Regulation Reports (Box 11, Folder 10)
- The Villages, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  July 4
- Wagner, Patricia F. Teaching in America (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Warner Cable's Qube: Exploring the Outer Reaches of Two-Way TV. Broadcasting., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  July 31
- Weber, Arnold R. Variety in Adaptation to Technological Change (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Weggeland, Daniel W. The Mediator: America's collective Bargaining Catalyst Weinstein, David. The Future of the Legal Profession Part 2: Salvation Through Prepaid and Other Fictions (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Weinstein David. The Future of the Legal Profession Part 2: Salvation Through Prepaid and Others Fictions (Box 11, Folder 16)
- what's in your future? New York State School of ILR (Box 11, Folder 17)
- White, Arthur J. and Theodore W. Kheel. Policies and Procedures Under the Wage and Salary Stabilization Plan (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Why Kheel Opposes the Center. The Village Voice, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Williams, Leslie. Resolution of Impasses. Presented at the International Symposium on Public employment Labor Relations (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Wilson, Wesley M. Labor Law Handbook (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Your Next Office Executives Meeting (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Zagoria, Sam. Mediation: A Path to Campus Peace? Labor Review (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Zeller, Belle. Why Faculties Organize (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 12, Folder 2)
  2
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 12, Folder 3)
  3
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 12, Folder 4)
  4
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 12, Folder 5)
  5
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 12, Folder 6)
  6
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 13, Folder 1)
  7
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 13, Folder 2)
  8
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 13, Folder 3)
  9
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 13, Folder 4)
  10
- Labor Law: CB, Economic Coercion, Duties of Unions, Rights of Individual Employees (Box 13, Folder 5)
  (star)
- T.W.K.s Speeches & Articles (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Speeches & Articles National Office Management Association, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- First Dinner Script, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- WMCA, 1943-1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Speeches & Articles National War Labor Board Press Release, 1944 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- In the Wake of the National Relations Board, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Herman Cooper 50th Birthday Party, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- American Transit Association Address - Boston, Mass., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Sept 26
- The Responsibility of Municipal Gov't to Reserve Mass Transportation America transit Assoc., 1955 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Address by TWK National Urban League, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- New School for Social research, 1956-1970 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1956-1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Speech by TWK National Urban League Annual Conference, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Overseas Press Club, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- International House, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Office Executes Association of NY Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Ghana, 1957-1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- United States Information Agency, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Ethical Culture Society, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- National Urban League, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Farleigh Dickinson University, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Kheel, Theodore W. Changing Patterns of Labor Relations in 1959 American Management Association, Midwinter Personnel conference Palmer House, Chicago (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Feb 17
- American Civil Liberties Union, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Fund for the Republic, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- NYC Central Labor Council, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- National Broadcasting Co., 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- NY Chamber of Commerce: Pros and Cons - Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Correspondence, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- NY Chamber of Commerce: Pros and cons - Misc., 1961 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- National Metal Trades Association, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Columbia University Seminar On Labor, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  May 1
- Institute for Religious Social Studies, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Manhattan College, 1962-1968 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Speeches & Articles Urban League of Pittsburgh, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- How the 25-Hour Work Week Has Worked, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Hoboken Industrial Management Club, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- New England Council, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Speeches & Articles Law Students Civil Rights Research Council (Box 14, Folder 38)
- How the 25-hour Work Week Has Worked, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Kheel, Theodore W. The Newspaper Strike Columbia University Seminar on Labor, New York, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- University of Rhode Island, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- A Strike Deterrent for New York City, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Transcript Newsmakers (CBS), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  Sept 15
- International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Kheel, Theodore W. "A Policy of Labor Relations for 1964." Annual American Bakers Association Convention Industrial relations Committee Meeting Sherman house, Chicago, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  Oct 14
- Speeches & Articles New York County Lawyers Assoc., 1963-1964 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Rotary Club of New York, 1963-1966 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Speeches & Articles WCBS-Radio Let's Find Out, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Speeches & Articles Wins Radio (Box 14, Folder 49)
- (empty) (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Miscellaneous, 1963-1968 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Conference of Christians and Jews, Inc., 1963-1968 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- WABC, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Federal Bar Association, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Speeches & Articles WCBS-TV (Newsmakers) Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Speeches & Articles Industrial relations Research Association, 1963-1970 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (University of Illinois), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- University of Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Electric Heat Seminar, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Mount Holyoke College, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- National committee for Labor Israel, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Municipal Personnel Society, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Speeches & Articles Links (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Speeches & Articles United Federation of Teachers Local 2, AFL-CIO, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Speeches & Articles United Federation of Teachers Local 2, AFL-CIO, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Speeches & Articles University of Chicago, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Speeches & Articles Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Speeches & Articles Impact of Automation on Collective Bargaining and visa versa, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Industrial College of the Armed Forces, 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- National Electrical Contractor's Assoc., 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Speeches & Articles New York Industrial Relations Research Assoc., 1964-1969 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Speeches & Articles NYC School of Secretaries Assoc., 1964-1971 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Kheel, Theodore W. A Plan for Labor-Management Peace in NYC, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Speeches & Articles University of Pittsburgh (Box 14, Folder 75)
- International Association of Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Speeches & Articles Nassau County Bar Association, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Speeches & Articles Newspaper Strike and Dispute (Miscellaneous), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Speeches & Articles national Plans for progress Conference "Impact of Title VII" etc., 1965 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Speeches & Articles National Export Traffic League, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Federation of Jewish Philanthropes, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Speeches & Articles Harper & Row, Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Speeches & Articles Labor Department (Box 15, Folder 4)
- International Institute for Labor Studies, 1965-1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Harvard University, 1965-1969 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Hunter College, 1965-1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- speeches & Articles The Netherlands Consulate, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Municipal Association for Management and Administration, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- William Morrow and Company, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Freedom Budget for all Americans, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Speeches & Articles Simon and Schuster, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Speeches & Articles Urban Corps. (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Speeches & Articles United Jewish Appeal (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Speeches & Articles The United Teacher, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Speeches & Articles New Jersey Association of School Administrators, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Queens Lighthouse, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- International Stereotypes and Electrotypes Union, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Speeches & Articles Naval War College (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Speeches & Articles WNBC-TV Direct Line, 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Speeches & Articles New Jersey State Bar Association, 1966-1969 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Speeches & Articles National Academy of Arbitrators, 1966-1973 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Speeches & Articles Local 144 Hotel & Allied Service Employees Union (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Lotos Club Speeches & Articles, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Senate Committee on Commerce, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Aug 17
- International Conference on Automation, Full Employment, and a Balanced Economy Rome, Italy 1967 AFAE (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Montclair Board of Education, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Town and Village Synagogue, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Human Resources Administration, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Haryou - Act Inc., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Holy Name society, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- National committee for the Support of Public Schools, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- 52 Association, Inc., 1967 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- International Longshoremen's Association, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- B'nai B'rith Photographs TWK, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Speeches & Articles NYS Assoc of Electrical Contractors and Dealers (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Speeches & Articles Newark College of Engineering, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Speeches & Articles National Academy for Television Arts and Science, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Speeches & Articles Philip Lubliner Testimonial Dinner (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Speeches & Articles University of Maryland, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Speeches & Articles University of Hawaii, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Fairfield University, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Fordham University School of Law, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Hebrew Academy, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Fifth Avenue Association, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- The Urban Coalition Speeches and Articles, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Speeches & Articles Look (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Financial Executives Institute, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- The Ditchley Foundation Speeches and Articles, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Speeches and Articles WCBS-TV (Newsmakers) Excerpt, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  Dec 22
- International Public Relations Co., 1968 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- International Typographical Union, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- National Flexible Packaging Associations (Chase Bag Co.) Speeches and Articles, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Transcript New York Report, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  Jan 7
- Veterans of Foreign Wars Floyd Gibbons Post 500, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 56)